<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>San Deigo on WST</title>
    <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/cities/san-deigo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in San Deigo on WST</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://whileshetravels.github.io/cities/san-deigo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Eating in San Deigo</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/u.s.a./california/san-diego/eating/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/u.s.a./california/san-diego/eating/</guid>
      <description>We landed in Paris on January 4th and have been trying different restaurants since then. Never been disappointed even once. We could settle in Paris just for its food.
  Restaurant: Le Drop Café; Item: Croquette and fries     Restaurant: Le Bistrot des Augustins; Item: Salmon Gratin     Bakery: Ladurée; Item: Chocolate Hazelnut Macaron     Restaurant: A Deux Pas d’lci in La Havre; Item: Cod fillet with tart apples and new potatoes     Restaurant: A Deux Pas d’lci in La Havre; Crumble perry and chocolate praline     Cafe: La Palette; Item: Coffee eclair     Cafe: Strada cafe; Item: Breakfast of Champions     Cafe: Strada cafe; Item: Hot Chocolate     Restaurant: Traiteur Marocain at Marché des Enfants Rouges; Item: Couscous Kefta     Cafe: Le Lafon; Item: Mousse au chocolat     Restaurant: Le Korrigan; Item: Savory crepe     Restaurant: Le Korrigan; Item: Chocolate crepe     Restaurant: Chez Gladines; Item: Squids in basque sauce with potatoes     Restaurant: Boulettes; Item: Cod fish meatballs with mashed potatoes     Restaurant: Auguste (1 Michelin Star); Item: Gaspache de tomates et pastèques 100% naturel Pickles de betteraves couleurs     Restaurant: Auguste (1 Michelin Star); Lieu jaune, pistou de salicorne Minestrone de petits pois “téléphone”     Restaurant: Auguste (1 Michelin Star); Item: Soufflé Grand Marnier Glace au fromage blanc     Restaurant: Le Dénicheur; Item: Tomato Soupe du jour     Restaurant: Le Dénicheur; Item: Fondant Au Chocolate Coeur Praline     Restaurant: Le Cafe; Item: Tartare de Saumon     Cafe: Le Porte Pot; Item: Tuna     Restaurant: Garance (1 Michelin Star); Item: Pomme purée     Restaurant: Garance (1 Michelin Star); Item: Cod fish     Restaurant: Garance (1 Michelin Star); Item: Chocolate dessert     Restaurant: Le Boui Boui; Item: Petit camenbert with fig     Restaurant: Le Boui Boui; Item: Sorbets     Restaurant: La Cave Gourmande; Item: Fish soup     Restaurant: Au Petit Suisse; Item: Tuna with homemade ratatouille and pasta     Restaurant: Au Petit Suisse; Item: French Onion soup   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>