<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Croatia on WST</title>
    <link>http://example.org/countries/croatia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Croatia on WST</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/countries/croatia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Diocletian’s Palace, Split</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/croatia/diocletians-palace-split/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/croatia/diocletians-palace-split/</guid>
      <description>Diocletian’s Palace is one of the best preserved monuments of the Roman architecture in the world. Many people would say, “Split = Dioclentian’s Palace” though Split is much more than that. Nevertheless, being in Split, you have to visit this place and being in Split for 20 days, we used to pass this palace almost everyday and I would click a picture or two every damn time. This palace has been destroyed for most part, but the ruins remain and its ruins are wonderful too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eating in and around Split</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/croatia/eating-in-and-around-split/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/croatia/eating-in-and-around-split/</guid>
      <description>If you are a sea food lover, you have to visit Split, Croatia. We stayed in Split for 20 days, and though we cooked at home too, we tried out many restaurants especially the ones in the Old Town. I found most of the restaurants clean with excellent customer service and yes, everyone speaks in English in Split, it seems. We found the prices of our dishes pretty reasonable too and portion was always good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green market- Pazar, Split</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/croatia/green-market-pazar-split/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/croatia/green-market-pazar-split/</guid>
      <description>Situated near the silver Gate of the Diocletian’s Palace, Green market which is also called Pazar, is one of the most happening places of Split, and a great place to meet some locals. It is like a farmer’s market on a big level.
  Fresh fruits and vegetables   Currently in Split, I often visit this market and during morning, it is so lively. Today I bought dried figs and a big ass red capsicum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marjan hill, Split</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/croatia/marjan-hill-split/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/croatia/marjan-hill-split/</guid>
      <description>Marjan hill situated on the peninsula of Split is the soul of the city. Covered in a dense mediterranean Pine forest and surrounded by the sea and the city, it makes a great escape place from the hustle and bustle of the center.
  View of Split from the top   There are many things to do here. There is a beach called Bene here, where you could swim in summer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trogir, a day trip from Split</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/croatia/trogir-a-day-trip-from-split/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/croatia/trogir-a-day-trip-from-split/</guid>
      <description>Trogir is a beautiful sea side town along the coast of the Adriatic sea. Its center is listed as the UNESCO World heritage site. And if you are in Split for few days, this should definitely be on your list.
  The historic city of Trogir   HISTORY OF TROGIR
Trogir, whose name is derived from the Greek word “Tragos” meaning male goat, was founded by the Greeks in about 3rd BC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visiting Game of Thrones Filming Locations in Dubrovnik, Croatia</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/croatia/game-of-thrones-filming-locations-in-dubrovnik/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/croatia/game-of-thrones-filming-locations-in-dubrovnik/</guid>
      <description>So you are a GOT fan and happen to be in Dubrovnik. That only means you want to be at the same spot your favorite GOT characters stood/sat/laughed/cried/ate/made love once. Dubrovnik being King’s landing in GOT was the shooting location for many important scenes. I tried my best to visit most of them but being there in winter, and bad weather limited me from visiting every location. I will share whatever I was able to cover and also what I was unable to cover.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solin, a day trip from Split</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/croatia/solin-a-day-trip-from-split/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/croatia/solin-a-day-trip-from-split/</guid>
      <description>Solin is a town situated northeast of Split on the Adriatic sea and the river Jadro. Being the birthplace of emperor Diocletian, it was important both politically and religiously. It was previously called Salona and it was the capital of the Roman province of Dalmatia. You can imagine its importance for the Roman empire. If you happen to be interested in archaeology or like history, this is a place you must visit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starigrad fortress hike in Omis, day trip from Split</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/croatia/omis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/croatia/omis/</guid>
      <description>Omis is 25 Km/16 miles from Split and it makes a great day trip from Split. It is where the Cetina river meets the Adriatic sea, and you can imagine how beautiful that place would be.
  The view of Omis while hiking up the fortress   HOW TO REACH OMIS FROM SPLIT We took bus 60 which runs every half an hour. Though this bus started from the bus terminal Sukoisan, you can also catch it from the bus station by the Green Market intersection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plitvice Lakes National Park in winter</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/croatia/plitvice-lakes-national-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/croatia/plitvice-lakes-national-park/</guid>
      <description>Plitvice Lakes National Park situated in the Lika county, which is like the middle of Croatia, is one of the most visited sights in Croatia with about 1 million visitors each year, and for good reasons. It is a UNESCO World Heritage site and the largest park in Croatia. I don’t know how it is in summer, but in winter it is too damn beautiful. And we knew we have to visit this place when we were planning to stay in Croatia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solta Island, day trip from Split</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/croatia/solta-island/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/croatia/solta-island/</guid>
      <description>We had been thinking to go to another island as a day trip using a ferry since a long time, but in winter, ferries do not run as frequently as they do in summer. After doing some research, I found out the island of Solta is not one of most popular getaway islands, but it is beautiful and possible to do it as a day trip. It is situated 18 Km south of Split in the central Dalmatian archipelago and there is a ferry from Split which goes to Rogac, which is the main port of Solta.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Driving along the Adriatic coast in Croatia (Sibenik to Primosten)</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/croatia/sibenik-to-primosten-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/croatia/sibenik-to-primosten-drive/</guid>
      <description>We loved the drive along the Pacific highway in California and wanted to do something similar in Croatia too. The stage was set. We had a rented car, there was the Adriatic sea, and our destination was Primosten, a town situated on the Adriatic coast between Sibenik and Trogir.
  One of the many coves we came across while driving from Sibenik to Primosten   We spent our Sunday morning at St Anthony’s channel in Sibenik, hiking with locals, and after finishing the hike, we were ready to go to Primosten.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St Anthony’s Channel in Sibenik, Croatia</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/croatia/st-anthonys-channel-in-sibenik/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/croatia/st-anthonys-channel-in-sibenik/</guid>
      <description>Having rented a car for two days in Split, we went to Plitvice lakes national park on day 1 and on day 2, we wanted to spend sometime in Sibenik before driving through the coast to Primosten. Sibenik is a town situated in the middle of the Adriatic coast. It is where Krka flows into the Adriatic sea. There are a lot of attractions here but rather than going into the main town, we chose to visit St Anthony’s channel.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>