<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on WST</title>
    <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on WST</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Iceland road trip itinerary</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/iceland-road-trip-itinerary/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/iceland-road-trip-itinerary/</guid>
      <description>I am sure you must have had several road trips in your life because come on who does not like a road trip? Right? But honestly, the one in Iceland is nothing like you have had before. It is beautiful to such an extent that it feels surreal. Yes, you might have seen like unlimited pictures of Iceland by now because these days Iceland is a hot tourist spot, but let me tell you something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iceland road trip: Day 1, April 23, 2017</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-1/</guid>
      <description>Driving route: Southwest to Northwest Attractions: No major attractions really Campsite for the night: Ólafsvik campsite We had our flight to Iceland Keflavik International airport at 8 AM from Copenhagen International airport. It was a 3.5 hour flight. The flight was 40% empty. We reached Keflavik around 9:30 AM. Yes, it is 2 hour behind the Central European time zone.
  Flying away to my dream destination   We had scheduled a pickup from our camper car company, which is Kuku Campers (read more about them here) at 10:00 AM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iceland road trip: Day 2, April 24, 2017</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-2/</guid>
      <description>Driving route: Northwest to North Attractions: Kirkjufell Mountain and Eiríksstadir farmhouse Campsite for the night: Hamrar in Akureyri On day 2 of our Iceland road trip, we woke up to this in our camper car at the campsite Olafsvik.
  We stepped outside and it was chilly and beautiful. Everything was covered with a thin sheet of snow and it seemed white mountains are calling me. But before that, we had to have our breakfast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iceland road trip: Day 3, April 25, 2017</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-3/</guid>
      <description>Driving route: North to East Attractions: Godafoss waterfall, Mývatn lake area (Skútustaðagígar pseudo craters, Dimmuborgir, Grjotagja Cave, Myvatn nature bath, and Mt. Námafjall) Campsite for the night: Egilsstadir Camping site Having slept soundly previous night at Hamrar campsite in Akureyri, we woke up fresh and all set to explore the east Iceland. But first thing first. We took shower which was what we really needed. Then, we fixed ourselves some eggs and bread in the kitchen of our campsite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iceland road trip: Day 4, April 26, 2017</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-4/</guid>
      <description>Driving route: East to South East Attractions: Jökulsárlón - Glacier Lagoon Campsite for the night: Vatnajökull National Park campsite Day 4 was the sunniest and hottest day in Iceland for us, and also the most beautiful day. Our objective for today was to reach south east and camp at Skaftafell National Park, which is actually a part of Vatnajökull National Park now.
Our last night campsite, Egilsstadir, was equipped with hot shower.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iceland road trip: Day 5, April 27, 2017</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-5/</guid>
      <description>Driving route: South East to south Attractions: Vatnajökull glacier, Svartifoss waterfall, Fjaðrárgljúfur canyon, Laufskálavarða, Mossy Lava Rock Black Sand Beach, Skogafoss Campsite for the night: Gesthús Selfoss Campsite We spent the last night in the parking lot of the Vatnajökull National Park. Vatnajökull is the largest glacier in Europe and you can even do glacier hiking, if you like that sort of things. You can find two different tour companies in the National park itself which do glacier hiking and ice caving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iceland road trip: Day 6, April 28, 2017</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-6/</guid>
      <description>Driving route: South to Southwest (Golden Circle) Attractions: Þingvellir National Park, Geysir, Gullfoss waterfall Campsite for the night: Gesthús Selfoss Campsite It was Friday and day 6 of our Iceland road trip. Weather was not looking good for today. There was a high speed wind warning in the south. So, we wanted to keep things calm and light for today. We woke up sort of late. It had rained all night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iceland road trip: Day 7, April 29, 2017</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-7/</guid>
      <description>Driving route: South to Southwest (Golden Circle) Attractions: Kerið crater lake, Skalholt, Secret Lagoon, Laugarvatn Fontana, Hrunalaug hot spring, Brúarfoss, Faxi (waterfall) Campsite for the night: Gesthús Selfoss Campsite Day 7 was our last day with our camping car. We were supposed to drop it off the next day in the morning. There were few things we wanted to cover, but to a large extent, we had kept this day open to see things as we drive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reykjavik, Iceland: Day 8, April 30, 2017</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-8/</guid>
      <description>Driving route: Gesthús Selfoss campsite to Kuku campers. Kuku campers to Reykjavik by bus. Attractions: Laugavegur shopping and dining area Campsite for the night: No campsite. Finally an Airbnb place. So, it was almost all over. Our Iceland road trip. And not only that, our 5 months of country hopping was coming to an end too. We weren&amp;rsquo;t thinking a lot about going back to the US at this time though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reykjavik, Iceland: Day 9, May 1, 2017</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-9/</guid>
      <description>Attractions: Hallgrimskirkja, Solfar/Sun Voyager sculpture, Harpa Reykjavik Concert Hall and Conference Centre, Lake Tjornin It was raining hard on day 9, which was also our last day of our Iceland trip. To be more precise, the whole Euro trip. We did not want to go out really, but of course, we did go out. I did not want to waste my last day just like that.
Our first stop was Hallgrimskirkja, a Lutheran Parish church, which also happens to be the tallest church in Iceland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brasov, a medieval city surrounded by the Carpathian Mountains</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/brasov/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/brasov/</guid>
      <description>Brasov pronounced as Bra-Shov is one of the most visited cities of Romania. Located in the center of Romania, it makes a perfect base for exploring the surrounding regions and trust me, you do wanna go see those surrounding regions. Why? Well, I am sure your trip to Romania is incomplete without visiting the Bran Castle and Bran castle is only a 40 minute bus ride from Brasov. Similarly, there are many other cool things to see around Brasov, which I would mention later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hiking to the Seven Ladders Canyon, a unique experience near Brasov in Romania</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/seven-ladders-canyon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/seven-ladders-canyon/</guid>
      <description>Our Airbnb host suggested us to hike to the Seven Ladders Canyon also known Canionul Sapte Scari in Romania. 7 Laderrs Canyon lies in Piatra Mare Mountains and if you enjoy hiking and some adrenaline rush, this is the place you need to be. Many people visiting Brasov don’t know about it, but it is pretty popular with locals. We were staying for a total of 10 days in Brasov and we thought why not, let’s do some hiking, which would be a good change from all the sightseeings we’d been doing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A day in Iguazu Falls</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/argentina/iguazu-falls/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/argentina/iguazu-falls/</guid>
      <description>Iguazu falls are waterfalls of the Iguazu River on the border of the Argentine province of Misiones and the Brazilian state of Paraná. Together, they make up the largest waterfall system in the world. The falls divide the river into the upper and lower Iguazu.
The name Iguazú meaning water and big. Legend has it that a deity planned to marry a beautiful woman named Naipí, who fled with her mortal lover Tarobá in a canoe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Altaplantis Lagoons</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/chile/san-pedro-de-atacama/altipanic-lakes-hike/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/chile/san-pedro-de-atacama/altipanic-lakes-hike/</guid>
      <description>Tour Operator Guide Time     Chakana tours Jaime 6:00 - 15:00    Chaxa Lagoon Altitude: 2300m
  Had three kinds of flamingos. Learned that flamingoes Andean, James, and Chilean
Flamingos are pink or orange or white depending on what they eat. Flamingos eat algae and crustaceans that contain pigments called carotenoids. For the most part, these pigments are found in the brine shrimp and blue-green algae that the birds eat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geysors El Tatio</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/chile/san-pedro-de-atacama/geysors-el-tatio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/chile/san-pedro-de-atacama/geysors-el-tatio/</guid>
      <description>Tour Operator Guide Time     Andes Travels Jaime 5:00 - 13:00    Height: 4320m
  Dress: Layers of clothes and multiple socks. The ground is literally freezing.
Restrooms: Are pretty cleaned and widely available
Animals seen: Lamas and Fox and Vicuña and Lamas
Caution: Altitude sickness so walk slowly and small steps Drink a lot of water.
Stopped at a Machucha to have Queso De Cabra (Empananadas with Goat Cheese) very delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lascar Volcano hike</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/chile/san-pedro-de-atacama/lascar-volcano-hike/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/chile/san-pedro-de-atacama/lascar-volcano-hike/</guid>
      <description>Láscar volcano in northern Chile is the most active of the northern Chilean Andes. Lascar is an andesitic-to-dacitic stratovolcano with 3 overlapping summit craters. Large lava flows are visible on its NW flanks. Lascar is flanked 5 km to the east by the older, but higher Volcán Aguas Calientes stratovolcano.
  Crater   The most important ones are Licancabut, Sairecabur, Llullolico (the three at the international border), Lascar, Paniri, Linzor volcanoes stand at 5500m above sea levels, therefore it is fundamental to spend a few days adaoptinh to the altitude.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moon and Death Valley</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/chile/san-pedro-de-atacama/moon-and-death-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/chile/san-pedro-de-atacama/moon-and-death-valley/</guid>
      <description>Moon valley It is one of the most visited places in San Pedro and it is located at 17 kilometers of San Pedro&amp;rsquo;s downtown, in the Cordillera de la Sal (Salt mountains) area, is an interesting area with stones and sand formations that per millenia the floods and the winds have given it a series of colors and texture to the desert, it presents an extraordinary attractive by its similarity with the moon surface and the natural coliseo of great dimensions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mostar, a day trip from Sarajevo</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/bosnia/mostar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/bosnia/mostar/</guid>
      <description>The historic town of Mostar spanning a deep valley of Neretva river must be on your list if you are in Bosnia and Herzegovina. It is famous for its medieval arched bridge called Stari Most or the Old Bridge built during the Ottoman empire rule, and now there is something else which is gaining popularity worldwide and it is the cliff diving competition. If you do not have enough time, this can easily be a day trip from Sarajevo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Pedro de Atacama Itinerary</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/chile/san-pedro-de-atacama/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/chile/san-pedro-de-atacama/summary/</guid>
      <description>The most arid desert in th world, the Atcama Desert. The archealogoical capital of Chile is located at tee base of the High Lands, at the basin of the San Pedro River(the biggest river to reach the Atacam Salt Flats). The basins borders the Domeyko Mountain Range to the west and the high plateau or Altiplano of the Andes Mountain Range or the Puna de Atacam to the east</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 things to do in Sarajevo, Bosnia and Herzegovina</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/bosnia/top-10-things-to-do-in-sarajevo-bosnia/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/bosnia/top-10-things-to-do-in-sarajevo-bosnia/</guid>
      <description>Sarajevo is an easygoing relaxing city representing both eastern and western culture. You can find a mosque and a church both in the same neighborhood, which is incredible. Europe is not cheap, but Sarajevo is a place where you can stay for few days lavishly. Food is not only good but cheap too. People though still tormented by the last war are friendly and hospitable, and most of them speak English.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trebević mountain hike</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/bosnia/trebevic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/bosnia/trebevic/</guid>
      <description>Trebević mountain is so close to Sarajevo yet it feels so far. It was one of the favorite hangout places for Sarajevans before the war. During the war, heavy fighting took place here and most of the infrastructures got destroyed. A good portion of Trebević was mined, but it is pretty safe now, but one still gotta be careful.
  We had heard so much good things about the mountains in Bosnia and Herzegovina, and we really wanted to hike at least one of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tunnel of Hope, Sarajevo</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/bosnia/tunnelofhope/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/bosnia/tunnelofhope/</guid>
      <description>As the name suggests, the Tunnel of Hope or the Sarajevo War Tunnel was the only hope for Sarajevans during the time of the Bosnian war. During the siege of Sarajevo, Serbian forces had entirely cut off Sarajevo from the outside world, and this tunnel was the only means of connection of Sarajevo with Bosnian-held territory on the other side of the Sarajevo airport, which was under the control of the United Nations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two weeks in Buenos Aires</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/argentina/buenos-aires/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/argentina/buenos-aires/</guid>
      <description>Buenos Aires is the capital and largest city of Argentina. The city is located on the western shore of the estuary of the Río de la Plata, on the South American continent&amp;rsquo;s southeastern coast. Buenos Aires can be translated as fair winds or good airs, but the former was the meaning intended by the founders in the 16th century, by the use of the original name Real de Nuestra Señora Santa María del Buen Ayre.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diocletian’s Palace, Split</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/croatia/diocletians-palace-split/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/croatia/diocletians-palace-split/</guid>
      <description>Diocletian’s Palace is one of the best preserved monuments of the Roman architecture in the world. Many people would say, “Split = Dioclentian’s Palace” though Split is much more than that. Nevertheless, being in Split, you have to visit this place and being in Split for 20 days, we used to pass this palace almost everyday and I would click a picture or two every damn time. This palace has been destroyed for most part, but the ruins remain and its ruins are wonderful too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eating in and around Split</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/croatia/eating-in-and-around-split/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/croatia/eating-in-and-around-split/</guid>
      <description>If you are a sea food lover, you have to visit Split, Croatia. We stayed in Split for 20 days, and though we cooked at home too, we tried out many restaurants especially the ones in the Old Town. I found most of the restaurants clean with excellent customer service and yes, everyone speaks in English in Split, it seems. We found the prices of our dishes pretty reasonable too and portion was always good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the villages of Romania, not far from Sibiu ( Marginimea Sibiului)</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/marginimea-sibiului/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/marginimea-sibiului/</guid>
      <description>Marginimea Sibiului which means “ Borders of Sibiu” is an area which is made up of 18 villages. Set at the foothills of the Cindrel Mountains, the villages are known for preserving the ethnological, cultural, architectural, and historical heritage of Romania. Even now, people wear traditional Romanian costumes, and their occupation is shepherding. They take the sheep to the mountains in summer and bring them back to the village in winter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green market- Pazar, Split</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/croatia/green-market-pazar-split/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/croatia/green-market-pazar-split/</guid>
      <description>Situated near the silver Gate of the Diocletian’s Palace, Green market which is also called Pazar, is one of the most happening places of Split, and a great place to meet some locals. It is like a farmer’s market on a big level.
  Fresh fruits and vegetables   Currently in Split, I often visit this market and during morning, it is so lively. Today I bought dried figs and a big ass red capsicum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marjan hill, Split</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/croatia/marjan-hill-split/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/croatia/marjan-hill-split/</guid>
      <description>Marjan hill situated on the peninsula of Split is the soul of the city. Covered in a dense mediterranean Pine forest and surrounded by the sea and the city, it makes a great escape place from the hustle and bustle of the center.
  View of Split from the top   There are many things to do here. There is a beach called Bene here, where you could swim in summer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nice</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/nice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/nice/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nice (/ˈniːs/, French pronunciation: ​[nis]; Niçard Occitan: Niça, classical norm, or Nissa, nonstandard, pronounced [ˈnisa]; Italian: Nizza [ˈnittsa]; Greek: Νίκαια; Latin: Nicaea) is the fifth most populous city in France and the capital of the Alpes-Maritimes département. The urban area of Nice extends beyond the administrative city limits, with a population of about 1 million[1][2] on an area of 721 km2 (278 sq mi).[1] Located in the French Riviera, on the south east coast of France on the Mediterranean Sea, at the foot of the Alps, Nice is the second-largest French city on the Mediterranean coast and the second-largest city in the Provence-Alpes-Côte d&amp;rsquo;Azur region after Marseille. Nice is about 13 kilometres (8 miles) from the principality of Monaco, and its airport is a gateway to the principality as well.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One day in Budapest, Hungary</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/hungary/budapest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/hungary/budapest/</guid>
      <description>So, you wanna see the beautiful city of Budapest and you do not have enough time. D and I had the same problem and D did not even want to be here just for a day, but I somehow managed to plan this trip and it went well. I am leaving Budapest right now for Vienna and I am writing this on a bus. Ha.
  There is no other place like Budapest!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trogir, a day trip from Split</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/croatia/trogir-a-day-trip-from-split/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/croatia/trogir-a-day-trip-from-split/</guid>
      <description>Trogir is a beautiful sea side town along the coast of the Adriatic sea. Its center is listed as the UNESCO World heritage site. And if you are in Split for few days, this should definitely be on your list.
  The historic city of Trogir   HISTORY OF TROGIR
Trogir, whose name is derived from the Greek word “Tragos” meaning male goat, was founded by the Greeks in about 3rd BC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peles Castle, day trip from Brasov</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/peles-castle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/peles-castle/</guid>
      <description>Bran castle is interesting and all thanks to Bram Stoker and Vlad the impaler, but honestly it is a rather simple castle and one not so impressive. Many people come out from there disappointed. If you really wanna see a castle at a grand level near Brasov, you should head to a town of Sinaia and walk to the Peles castle. It is one of the most picturesque and stylish castles in Europe, with extremely well-preserved architecture, details and furniture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alba Iulia, day trip from Sibiu</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/alba-iulia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/alba-iulia/</guid>
      <description>We first came to know about Alba Iulia from our Airbnb host, Diana, in Timisoara. We had to go to Sibiu from Timisoara and the bus ride was about 6 hours. Diana suggested we go to Alba Iulia first, stay there for a night, and then go to Sibiu. It did not work out for us as we had already booked an Airbnb apartment in Sibiu. In Sibiu, our host also mentioned Alba Iulia that we can easily do a day trip from Sibiu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bran castle and Rasnov citadel, day trip from Brasov</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/bran-castle-and-rasnov-citadel-a-day-trip-from-brasov/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/bran-castle-and-rasnov-citadel-a-day-trip-from-brasov/</guid>
      <description>When you are in Romania, and haven’t visited Bran castle aka Dracula’s castle, nobody would believe you have been to Romania. Romania is famous for its Dracula’s story and Vlad the impaler, who has been referred to as a vampire/Dracula due to his torture methods, but obviously, those are just legends, which became popular due to Bram Stoker’s novel, Dracula. Romania is famous for all the wrong reasons, it seems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balea Lake in winter, a day trip from Sibiu</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/balea-lake/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/balea-lake/</guid>
      <description>Balea lake is a glacier lake close to Sibiu. It takes about an hour to get there by car. Situated at the height of 2,034 m in the Fagaras mountains, it is covered with snow for most part. In summer, you can drive to it via the Transfăgărășan road. We really wanted to drive through the Transfăgărășan road, but it is open only from July to September, unfortunately, due to heavy snow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sibiu, an idyllic medieval town in Romania</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/sibiu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/sibiu/</guid>
      <description>Sibiu was our second destination in Romania, first being Timisoara. Both the cities are so distinct from each other. Where Timisoara is a big city by the standard of Romania, Sibiu is more like a town, to be more precise, a German town, with a total population of 147,245. Sibiu is located in Transylvania region, which is the most interesting part of Romania. It was one of the seven cities in Transylvania with German settlers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diana and John, our Airbnb hosts</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/diana-and-john-our-airbnb-hosts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/diana-and-john-our-airbnb-hosts/</guid>
      <description>It’s been 4 months since we left our apartment in San Francisco to travel Europe. We have been to many places, seen a lot of wonderful things, met some really interesting people, but something which we would never forget is the hospitality of Diana and John. We stayed with them for 2 nights at their apartment located centrally in Timisoara via Airbnb. We came as strangers and left as friends. Both Diana and John are lovely people and they make such a cute couple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sighisoara, day trip from Brasov</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/sighisoara-day-trip-from-brasov/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/sighisoara-day-trip-from-brasov/</guid>
      <description>Ever since coming to Romania, everybody kept talking about how we have to visit Sighisoara, the only living citadel in Europe. When we were in Sibiu, our guide suggested us to take us there, but we thought we would do this as a day trip from Brasov as we had more days there. In Brasov, one of the first things our Airbnb host told us was to go get lost in Sighisoara.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top things to do in Timisoara, Romania</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/top-things-to-do-in-timisoara-romania/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/top-things-to-do-in-timisoara-romania/</guid>
      <description>We had heard and read a lot about Romania from the stories of Dracula to this country having one of the fastest internets in the world, and this was on our bucket list since a long time. The first city we decided to explore in Romania was Timisoara as it was only a 3 hour drive from Belgrade, where we stayed for 2 weeks. Timisoara is the third most populous country in Romania and being the European Cultural Capital for 2021, it offers a lot of things to do, and most of the important landmarks are situated in the city center or close to the city center.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kalemegdan park and Belgrade fortress</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/serbia/kalemegdan-park-and-belgrade-fortress/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/serbia/kalemegdan-park-and-belgrade-fortress/</guid>
      <description>Kalemegdan Park is the Central Park of Belgrade, which means it is the largest and most beautiful park in Belgrade. It name comes from two Turkish words: Kale meaning fortress and megdan meaning battlefield. Kalemegdan park is basically a part of the Belgrade fortress and if there is only one thing you could do in Belgrade, it has to be visiting this fortress along with the park.
  Kalemegdan Park Fortress   HISTORY OF THE BELGRADE FORTRESS</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knez Mihailova Street, Belgrade</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/serbia/knez-mihailova-street-belgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/serbia/knez-mihailova-street-belgrade/</guid>
      <description>If you wanna feel the pulse of Belgrade, take a walk on the most vibrant street of this city, Knez Mihailova Street, which starts at Terazije Square and ends at Kalemegdan Park.
  Knez	Mihailova	Street   Knez Mihailova Street named after Mihailo Obrenović III, Prince of Serbia, is the main pedestrian and shopping zone protected by the law as the oldest and most valuable landmark of Belgrade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kosancicev venac, Belgrade</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/serbia/kosancicev-venac-belgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/serbia/kosancicev-venac-belgrade/</guid>
      <description>Kosancicev venac is the oldest urban neighborhood in Belgrade, where I am staying at present. Right now it is under construction, but that doesn’t take away its charm. Its Turkish cobblestones, cafes, galleries, and wineries give it the atmosphere of the 19th century.
  The neighborhood of Kosancicev venac ST. MICHAEL’S CATHEDRAL/SABORNA CRKVA
Though it is not the center of the city, it is close to many important landmarks like Kalemegdan park and fortress, Knez Mihailova Street, Republic Square in Belgrade, and this neighborhood boasts of one of the most beautiful Orthodox churches in the world, called St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Novi Sad, Serbia</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/serbia/novisad-belgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/serbia/novisad-belgrade/</guid>
      <description>Novi Sad is the second largest city in Serbia after Belgrade, famous for its Exit festival. It is on the banks of the Danube River and is absolutely gorgeous to the point that if there were such competition as being the most beautiful city in Serbia, it would give a very healthy competition to Belgrade. Being only 58 miles/94 Km from Belgrade, it makes a perfect day trip from Belgrade, though spending a night or two would be good too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Republic Square, Belgrade</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/serbia/republic-square-belgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/serbia/republic-square-belgrade/</guid>
      <description>Republic Square is one of the most common meeting points for both locals and visitors. If you are going on a tour with a local tour company, they would ask you to meet them “Under the Horse” which is just another name for Republic Square. Why? Because of the Monument to Prince Mihailo Obrenovic.
  Monument to Prince Mihailo Obrenovic. You can see why it’s called “Under the Horse   Besides the statue of Prince Mihailo, you can also find the National Museum and the National Theatre at Republic Square.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skadarlija/Bohemian quarter, Belgrade</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/serbia/skadarlija-bohemian-quarter-belgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/serbia/skadarlija-bohemian-quarter-belgrade/</guid>
      <description>Skadarlija is a vintage street close to the city center of Belgrade. It is also called Bohemian quarter similar to Paris’ Montmartre. Though it is not as bohemian in nature as it was once, it has still maintained its old atmosphere and spirit to some extent and you can find cobblestone pavements here.
  Skadarlija street   This street is named after the old Serbian town Skadar, which is on the territory of Albania today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Church of Saint Sava, Belgrade</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/serbia/church-of-saint-sava/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/serbia/church-of-saint-sava/</guid>
      <description>The Church of Saint Sava, dedicated to Saint Sava, is one of the largest Orthodox churches in the world and the largest in the Balkans, located on the Vračar plateau in Belgrade. It is a pretty impressive church, looking majestic from the outside with its bright white walls, golden crosses and plump domes, but going inside, you feel a little disappointed as it is not completed yet. It is called the Basílica de la Sagrada Familia of Barcelona for obvious reasons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nikola Tesla Museum, Belgrade</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/serbia/nikola-tesla-museum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/serbia/nikola-tesla-museum/</guid>
      <description>Nikola Tesla is my all time favorite scientists and if you are into science, I am sure you admire him too. For those people who don&amp;rsquo;t know much about Tesla, he was born in a Serbian family in a Croatian town of Smiljan in 1856. This is the reason why both Serbia and Croatia are so proud of him. In Serbia, he is like everywhere from Tesla TV to Tesla 100 Dinar bill.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visiting Game of Thrones Filming Locations in Dubrovnik, Croatia</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/croatia/game-of-thrones-filming-locations-in-dubrovnik/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/croatia/game-of-thrones-filming-locations-in-dubrovnik/</guid>
      <description>So you are a GOT fan and happen to be in Dubrovnik. That only means you want to be at the same spot your favorite GOT characters stood/sat/laughed/cried/ate/made love once. Dubrovnik being King’s landing in GOT was the shooting location for many important scenes. I tried my best to visit most of them but being there in winter, and bad weather limited me from visiting every location. I will share whatever I was able to cover and also what I was unable to cover.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solin, a day trip from Split</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/croatia/solin-a-day-trip-from-split/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/croatia/solin-a-day-trip-from-split/</guid>
      <description>Solin is a town situated northeast of Split on the Adriatic sea and the river Jadro. Being the birthplace of emperor Diocletian, it was important both politically and religiously. It was previously called Salona and it was the capital of the Roman province of Dalmatia. You can imagine its importance for the Roman empire. If you happen to be interested in archaeology or like history, this is a place you must visit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starigrad fortress hike in Omis, day trip from Split</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/croatia/omis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/croatia/omis/</guid>
      <description>Omis is 25 Km/16 miles from Split and it makes a great day trip from Split. It is where the Cetina river meets the Adriatic sea, and you can imagine how beautiful that place would be.
  The view of Omis while hiking up the fortress   HOW TO REACH OMIS FROM SPLIT We took bus 60 which runs every half an hour. Though this bus started from the bus terminal Sukoisan, you can also catch it from the bus station by the Green Market intersection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plitvice Lakes National Park in winter</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/croatia/plitvice-lakes-national-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/croatia/plitvice-lakes-national-park/</guid>
      <description>Plitvice Lakes National Park situated in the Lika county, which is like the middle of Croatia, is one of the most visited sights in Croatia with about 1 million visitors each year, and for good reasons. It is a UNESCO World Heritage site and the largest park in Croatia. I don’t know how it is in summer, but in winter it is too damn beautiful. And we knew we have to visit this place when we were planning to stay in Croatia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luxembourg Garden/Jardin du Luxembourg</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/luxembourg-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/luxembourg-garden/</guid>
      <description>Luxembourg Garden is nothing you have not seen before, but to find such a spacious place in Paris which is ideal for both children and adults is not easy, and that’s what makes this garden so special.
  Just relaxing in the garden with the view of the Palace   Luxembourg Garden is situated on the Left Bank and it is well maintained. It has a lot of benches and chairs and we were just sitting there for almost an hour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solta Island, day trip from Split</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/croatia/solta-island/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/croatia/solta-island/</guid>
      <description>We had been thinking to go to another island as a day trip using a ferry since a long time, but in winter, ferries do not run as frequently as they do in summer. After doing some research, I found out the island of Solta is not one of most popular getaway islands, but it is beautiful and possible to do it as a day trip. It is situated 18 Km south of Split in the central Dalmatian archipelago and there is a ferry from Split which goes to Rogac, which is the main port of Solta.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Driving along the Adriatic coast in Croatia (Sibenik to Primosten)</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/croatia/sibenik-to-primosten-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/croatia/sibenik-to-primosten-drive/</guid>
      <description>We loved the drive along the Pacific highway in California and wanted to do something similar in Croatia too. The stage was set. We had a rented car, there was the Adriatic sea, and our destination was Primosten, a town situated on the Adriatic coast between Sibenik and Trogir.
  One of the many coves we came across while driving from Sibenik to Primosten   We spent our Sunday morning at St Anthony’s channel in Sibenik, hiking with locals, and after finishing the hike, we were ready to go to Primosten.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St Anthony’s Channel in Sibenik, Croatia</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/croatia/st-anthonys-channel-in-sibenik/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/croatia/st-anthonys-channel-in-sibenik/</guid>
      <description>Having rented a car for two days in Split, we went to Plitvice lakes national park on day 1 and on day 2, we wanted to spend sometime in Sibenik before driving through the coast to Primosten. Sibenik is a town situated in the middle of the Adriatic coast. It is where Krka flows into the Adriatic sea. There are a lot of attractions here but rather than going into the main town, we chose to visit St Anthony’s channel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disneyland Paris</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/disneyland-paris/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/disneyland-paris/</guid>
      <description>We were really tired doing this sightseeing and wanted to do something different. Having never been the Disneyland Florida before, we thought let’s try the one here in Paris. We knew this one is not as good as the one in Florida after doing a ton of research, but it was worth a shot and I was in a mood of some adrenaline rush.
    View this post on Instagram         A post shared by @whileshetravels on Jan 31, 2017 at 11:27am PST</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Notre Dame de Paris</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/notre-dame-de-paris/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/notre-dame-de-paris/</guid>
      <description>Notre Dame de Paris meaning “Our Lady of Paris” is one of the largest and famous churches in the world. It is a fine example of Gothic architecture and being in Paris, if you do not see the Notre Dame de Paris, even just the cathedral which is free, it is really your loss. If possible, make sure you go all the way up the tower (not free) and admire the city of lights and gargoyles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eating in Mexico city</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/mexico/eating-in-mexico-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/mexico/eating-in-mexico-city/</guid>
      <description>We landed in Paris on January 4th and have been trying different restaurants since then. Never been disappointed even once. We could settle in Paris just for its food.
  Restaurant: Le Drop Café; Item: Croquette and fries     Restaurant: Le Bistrot des Augustins; Item: Salmon Gratin     Bakery: Ladurée; Item: Chocolate Hazelnut Macaron     Restaurant: A Deux Pas d’lci in La Havre; Item: Cod fillet with tart apples and new potatoes     Restaurant: A Deux Pas d’lci in La Havre; Crumble perry and chocolate praline     Cafe: La Palette; Item: Coffee eclair     Cafe: Strada cafe; Item: Breakfast of Champions     Cafe: Strada cafe; Item: Hot Chocolate     Restaurant: Traiteur Marocain at Marché des Enfants Rouges; Item: Couscous Kefta     Cafe: Le Lafon; Item: Mousse au chocolat     Restaurant: Le Korrigan; Item: Savory crepe     Restaurant: Le Korrigan; Item: Chocolate crepe     Restaurant: Chez Gladines; Item: Squids in basque sauce with potatoes     Restaurant: Boulettes; Item: Cod fish meatballs with mashed potatoes     Restaurant: Auguste (1 Michelin Star); Item: Gaspache de tomates et pastèques 100% naturel Pickles de betteraves couleurs     Restaurant: Auguste (1 Michelin Star); Lieu jaune, pistou de salicorne Minestrone de petits pois “téléphone”     Restaurant: Auguste (1 Michelin Star); Item: Soufflé Grand Marnier Glace au fromage blanc     Restaurant: Le Dénicheur; Item: Tomato Soupe du jour     Restaurant: Le Dénicheur; Item: Fondant Au Chocolate Coeur Praline     Restaurant: Le Cafe; Item: Tartare de Saumon     Cafe: Le Porte Pot; Item: Tuna     Restaurant: Garance (1 Michelin Star); Item: Pomme purée     Restaurant: Garance (1 Michelin Star); Item: Cod fish     Restaurant: Garance (1 Michelin Star); Item: Chocolate dessert     Restaurant: Le Boui Boui; Item: Petit camenbert with fig     Restaurant: Le Boui Boui; Item: Sorbets     Restaurant: La Cave Gourmande; Item: Fish soup     Restaurant: Au Petit Suisse; Item: Tuna with homemade ratatouille and pasta     Restaurant: Au Petit Suisse; Item: French Onion soup   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eating in Paris and around..</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/eating-in-paris-and-around/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/eating-in-paris-and-around/</guid>
      <description>We landed in Paris on January 4th and have been trying different restaurants since then. Never been disappointed even once. We could settle in Paris just for its food.
  Restaurant: Le Drop Café; Item: Croquette and fries     Restaurant: Le Bistrot des Augustins; Item: Salmon Gratin     Bakery: Ladurée; Item: Chocolate Hazelnut Macaron     Restaurant: A Deux Pas d’lci in La Havre; Item: Cod fillet with tart apples and new potatoes     Restaurant: A Deux Pas d’lci in La Havre; Crumble perry and chocolate praline     Cafe: La Palette; Item: Coffee eclair     Cafe: Strada cafe; Item: Breakfast of Champions     Cafe: Strada cafe; Item: Hot Chocolate     Restaurant: Traiteur Marocain at Marché des Enfants Rouges; Item: Couscous Kefta     Cafe: Le Lafon; Item: Mousse au chocolat     Restaurant: Le Korrigan; Item: Savory crepe     Restaurant: Le Korrigan; Item: Chocolate crepe     Restaurant: Chez Gladines; Item: Squids in basque sauce with potatoes     Restaurant: Boulettes; Item: Cod fish meatballs with mashed potatoes     Restaurant: Auguste (1 Michelin Star); Item: Gaspache de tomates et pastèques 100% naturel Pickles de betteraves couleurs     Restaurant: Auguste (1 Michelin Star); Lieu jaune, pistou de salicorne Minestrone de petits pois “téléphone”     Restaurant: Auguste (1 Michelin Star); Item: Soufflé Grand Marnier Glace au fromage blanc     Restaurant: Le Dénicheur; Item: Tomato Soupe du jour     Restaurant: Le Dénicheur; Item: Fondant Au Chocolate Coeur Praline     Restaurant: Le Cafe; Item: Tartare de Saumon     Cafe: Le Porte Pot; Item: Tuna     Restaurant: Garance (1 Michelin Star); Item: Pomme purée     Restaurant: Garance (1 Michelin Star); Item: Cod fish     Restaurant: Garance (1 Michelin Star); Item: Chocolate dessert     Restaurant: Le Boui Boui; Item: Petit camenbert with fig     Restaurant: Le Boui Boui; Item: Sorbets     Restaurant: La Cave Gourmande; Item: Fish soup     Restaurant: Au Petit Suisse; Item: Tuna with homemade ratatouille and pasta     Restaurant: Au Petit Suisse; Item: French Onion soup   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eating in San Deigo</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/u.s.a./california/san-diego/eating/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/u.s.a./california/san-diego/eating/</guid>
      <description>We landed in Paris on January 4th and have been trying different restaurants since then. Never been disappointed even once. We could settle in Paris just for its food.
  Restaurant: Le Drop Café; Item: Croquette and fries     Restaurant: Le Bistrot des Augustins; Item: Salmon Gratin     Bakery: Ladurée; Item: Chocolate Hazelnut Macaron     Restaurant: A Deux Pas d’lci in La Havre; Item: Cod fillet with tart apples and new potatoes     Restaurant: A Deux Pas d’lci in La Havre; Crumble perry and chocolate praline     Cafe: La Palette; Item: Coffee eclair     Cafe: Strada cafe; Item: Breakfast of Champions     Cafe: Strada cafe; Item: Hot Chocolate     Restaurant: Traiteur Marocain at Marché des Enfants Rouges; Item: Couscous Kefta     Cafe: Le Lafon; Item: Mousse au chocolat     Restaurant: Le Korrigan; Item: Savory crepe     Restaurant: Le Korrigan; Item: Chocolate crepe     Restaurant: Chez Gladines; Item: Squids in basque sauce with potatoes     Restaurant: Boulettes; Item: Cod fish meatballs with mashed potatoes     Restaurant: Auguste (1 Michelin Star); Item: Gaspache de tomates et pastèques 100% naturel Pickles de betteraves couleurs     Restaurant: Auguste (1 Michelin Star); Lieu jaune, pistou de salicorne Minestrone de petits pois “téléphone”     Restaurant: Auguste (1 Michelin Star); Item: Soufflé Grand Marnier Glace au fromage blanc     Restaurant: Le Dénicheur; Item: Tomato Soupe du jour     Restaurant: Le Dénicheur; Item: Fondant Au Chocolate Coeur Praline     Restaurant: Le Cafe; Item: Tartare de Saumon     Cafe: Le Porte Pot; Item: Tuna     Restaurant: Garance (1 Michelin Star); Item: Pomme purée     Restaurant: Garance (1 Michelin Star); Item: Cod fish     Restaurant: Garance (1 Michelin Star); Item: Chocolate dessert     Restaurant: Le Boui Boui; Item: Petit camenbert with fig     Restaurant: Le Boui Boui; Item: Sorbets     Restaurant: La Cave Gourmande; Item: Fish soup     Restaurant: Au Petit Suisse; Item: Tuna with homemade ratatouille and pasta     Restaurant: Au Petit Suisse; Item: French Onion soup   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eating in Tokyo</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/japan/tokyo/eating/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/japan/tokyo/eating/</guid>
      <description>We landed in Paris on January 4th and have been trying different restaurants since then. Never been disappointed even once. We could settle in Paris just for its food.
  Restaurant: Le Drop Café; Item: Croquette and fries     Restaurant: Le Bistrot des Augustins; Item: Salmon Gratin     Bakery: Ladurée; Item: Chocolate Hazelnut Macaron     Restaurant: A Deux Pas d’lci in La Havre; Item: Cod fillet with tart apples and new potatoes     Restaurant: A Deux Pas d’lci in La Havre; Crumble perry and chocolate praline     Cafe: La Palette; Item: Coffee eclair     Cafe: Strada cafe; Item: Breakfast of Champions     Cafe: Strada cafe; Item: Hot Chocolate     Restaurant: Traiteur Marocain at Marché des Enfants Rouges; Item: Couscous Kefta     Cafe: Le Lafon; Item: Mousse au chocolat     Restaurant: Le Korrigan; Item: Savory crepe     Restaurant: Le Korrigan; Item: Chocolate crepe     Restaurant: Chez Gladines; Item: Squids in basque sauce with potatoes     Restaurant: Boulettes; Item: Cod fish meatballs with mashed potatoes     Restaurant: Auguste (1 Michelin Star); Item: Gaspache de tomates et pastèques 100% naturel Pickles de betteraves couleurs     Restaurant: Auguste (1 Michelin Star); Lieu jaune, pistou de salicorne Minestrone de petits pois “téléphone”     Restaurant: Auguste (1 Michelin Star); Item: Soufflé Grand Marnier Glace au fromage blanc     Restaurant: Le Dénicheur; Item: Tomato Soupe du jour     Restaurant: Le Dénicheur; Item: Fondant Au Chocolate Coeur Praline     Restaurant: Le Cafe; Item: Tartare de Saumon     Cafe: Le Porte Pot; Item: Tuna     Restaurant: Garance (1 Michelin Star); Item: Pomme purée     Restaurant: Garance (1 Michelin Star); Item: Cod fish     Restaurant: Garance (1 Michelin Star); Item: Chocolate dessert     Restaurant: Le Boui Boui; Item: Petit camenbert with fig     Restaurant: Le Boui Boui; Item: Sorbets     Restaurant: La Cave Gourmande; Item: Fish soup     Restaurant: Au Petit Suisse; Item: Tuna with homemade ratatouille and pasta     Restaurant: Au Petit Suisse; Item: French Onion soup   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where to stay in Prague</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/where-to-stay-in-prague/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/where-to-stay-in-prague/</guid>
      <description>To be honest, I don’t have any idea about hotels in Prague as we never stayed at any of them. We were going to be in Prague for more than a month (33 nights) and needed a furnished apartment/studio where we could live somewhat like locals.
We did an extensive research on different websites and were able to find a great studio in an excellent location for 24,000 CZK for 33 nights at https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crécy-la-Chapelle</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/cre%CC%81cy-la-chapelle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/cre%CC%81cy-la-chapelle/</guid>
      <description>If you are in Paris and have seen everything, and want to get away from the City of lights and its crowd for some time, Crécy-la-Chapelle would be an ideal place to do so.
  Crécy-la-Chapelle   Crécy-la-Chapelle is a small town and you can call it a mini Venice. It takes only an hour from Paris. We had been thinking to visit this town since some time and after missing our train to Mont Saint Michel, we finally did it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mont Saint-Michel, the trip which we couldn’t make it.</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/mont-saint-michel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/mont-saint-michel/</guid>
      <description>Le Mont Saint-Michel, an island commune in Normandy, is one of the most popular day trips from Paris and obviously, we had our heart set on it long before we came to Paris. It is situated in the middle of the bay and is famous for its abbey and having been to Etretat, another commune in Normandy, I was super excited for Mont Saint-Michel. I am sorry I got no picture to show and don’t want to use any Google image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musée de l’Armée and Napoleon’s Tomb</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/musee-d-larmee-and-napoleons-tomb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/musee-d-larmee-and-napoleons-tomb/</guid>
      <description>The Musée de l’Armée or the Army museum as the name suggests exhibits France’s complete military history along with the tomb of Napoleon. It is a perfect place if you love history. Even if you do not, you should visit this museum just for Napoleon, the man who conquered almost every part of Europe.
We left at 11 in the morning and took metro, line 8 and got off at La Tour Mauborg.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musée d Louvre, Paris</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/musee-d-louvre/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/musee-d-louvre/</guid>
      <description>If you are an art lover, you don’t need any introduction to the Musée du Louvre, and if you are not, this is the museum where you find the famous Mona Lisa, Venus de Milo and more than 30,000 work of arts. We visited the Louvre after the Musée d&amp;rsquo;Orsay, which was not in the right order actually. The Louvre museum houses the art works from the ancient world to 1850 and the Orsay museum got stuff from 1850 onwards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Père Lachaise Cemetery</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/pe%CC%80re-lachaise-cemetery/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/pe%CC%80re-lachaise-cemetery/</guid>
      <description>Père Lachaise Cemetery is one of the most peaceful cemeteries I have ever been to not to mention it is quite big and free, and in the month of January, it was so calm that it gave a kind of an eerie feeling. I know all cemeteries do. It got about 5000 trees and does look like a park. It is a star cemetery filled with the tombs of Oscar Wilde to Jim Morrison.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Champs-Élysées</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/champs-e%CC%81lyse%CC%81es/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/champs-e%CC%81lyse%CC%81es/</guid>
      <description>I have always heard about the Avenue des Champs-Élysées pronounced as Shon-zay-LEE-zay, that how grand and Parisian this avenue is. Taking a stroll around this avenue on a rainy January night made me feel a Parisian too, temporarily. We took metro line 9 and got off at Franklin D Roosevelt and that’s where the Avenue des Champs-Élysées started.
  The Avenue of Champs-Élysées   Known for its cafes, theaters, branded shops, Bastille Day Military Parade and the Tour de France, Avenue des Champs-Élysées stretches between Place de la Concorde and the Arc de Triomphe, which is one of the most famous monuments in Paris.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Montmartre</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/montmartre/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/montmartre/</guid>
      <description>Montmartre is a hill situated in Paris’ 18 arrondissement and this neighborhood is quite different from the arrondissement we had been to. It is trendy, crowded, and kind of seedy, and a place where many famous people have lived or worked from Van Gogh to Pablo Picasso. Even now, there are many artists and portraitists working here to exhibit and sell their artwork.
  The view of Paris from the hill     Clear skies would have been better   We left on a Saturday afternoon using metro, line 4 and got off at Barbes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pont des Arts, Paris</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/pont-des-arts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/pont-des-arts/</guid>
      <description>Pont des Arts is that famous bridge where couples used to make their love for each other memorable by attaching love lock with their names engraved or written to the railing or the grate of the bridge and tossing the keys into the Seine river below. No, this trend did not start centuries ago. It was pretty recent. The year was 2008.
  The bridge links the domed Institut de France to the Louvre museum   I might have done the same with D though he would have disapproved for sure, but since 2014, the locks have been removed as they’re damaging the bridge with their weights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charles Bridge, Prague</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/charles-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/charles-bridge/</guid>
      <description>Charles Bridge is one of the most popular attractions in Prague. I don’t know what it is but there is something unique in the atmosphere on this bridge. It is too lively and everyone is super happy.
  Attempting to dab in the middle of the Charles Bridge! Not my fault. D forced me to.   Charles Bridge was built under Charles IV in 1357 and completed in 1402.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prague Castle Complex, Prague</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/prague-castle-complex/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/prague-castle-complex/</guid>
      <description>If you are in Prague and have not visited the castle, have you really been to Prague? The answer is no. Yes, we waited like forever to visit the famous castle for some unknown reason, but nonetheless, we did it and guess what we were rewarded with for our patience? Snow and a lot of it. Prague Castle is not just a castle but a castle complex and the largest one too in the world with an area of almost 70,000 meter squares.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Château de Versailles</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/versailles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/versailles/</guid>
      <description>Versailles is one of the most exquisite palaces of the world and a clear example of how pretentious kings used to be in the past. Started as a hunting lodge by Louis XIII in 1623, the Sun King, Louis XIV spent a great deal of money to convert his dad’s lodge into a grand palace.
  This whole damn thing looks like it is made of gold.   If you ask anyone for a day trip from Paris, Versailles would be the number one answer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prague Zoo, Prague</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/prague-zoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/prague-zoo/</guid>
      <description>Honestly, I was not expecting a lot from the zoo in Prague and I don’t even know why. Maybe because I thought Prague is all about the castle and cathedrals. I could not be more wrong. Prague zoo is full of exotic animals and it is well maintained with a lot of restrooms and cafes and restaurants. Also, it is a perfect getaway from the crowd and the various sightseeings we have been doing since a long time, and if you are in Prague with your kids, this is a place you must visit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Étretat, France</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/e%CC%81tretat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/e%CC%81tretat/</guid>
      <description>I was looking for a day trip from Paris and Étretat attracted me right away. It is a beautiful small town in Normandie region of France, with pebble beaches and unique shaped cliffs and arches. It takes about 3.5 hours one way from Paris to reach Etretat. I do not think I can justify its beauty in my post, but I would try and pictures would help.
  The serenity!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musée d&#39;Orsay, Paris</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/musee-d-orsay/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/musee-d-orsay/</guid>
      <description>Honestly, I have never been a museum enthusiast, but Paris is kind of a mecca of museums with the work of many world famous artists. The first place I visited in Paris was Musée d&amp;rsquo;Orsay pronounced as mew-zay-dor-say. Being one of the largest art museums in Paris, it houses the work of Manet, Monet, Cézanne, Van Gogh, Rodin, Gauguin and many other famous artists. You would find Impressionism at its best here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 days in Berlin, Germany</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/germany/2-days-in-berlin-germany/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/germany/2-days-in-berlin-germany/</guid>
      <description>Let me be very clear first. 2 days in Berlin is far from ideal, but hey, if you are running tight on the schedule, a couple of days in Berlin would give you a good impression of how this city is. We were in Berlin on christmas day and the day after. The christmas spirit was super high, as we expected.
  Berlin, a city with so much history!   After having spent a day in Dresden, we took a bus (flixbus) from Dresden at 8:30 AM and reached Berlin at 10:45 AM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A day in Dresden, Germany</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/germany/a-day-in-dresden-germany/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/germany/a-day-in-dresden-germany/</guid>
      <description>We wanted to visit a new place during christmas and we chose Germany. Close to Prague with so much crazy history. We started with visiting Dresden on the day of Christmas eve. We took a bus (Flixbus) from Praha hl.n. to Dresden hbf. It took us about 2 hours to get there. Pretty smooth ride.
  #Dresden2016   THE STRIEZELMARKT (CHRISTMAS MARKET)
If you are here during christmas (November 24 - December 24), the Striezelmarkt should be on the top of your list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Franz Kafka Museum, Prague</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/franz-kafka-museum/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/franz-kafka-museum/</guid>
      <description>“I am a cage, in search of a bird.” ― Franz Kafka
I read “Metamorphosis” by Franz Kafka in the summer of 2013 and honestly, I had never read a book like that. It did not make much sense to me and yet kept me intrigued. All that time I was reading, I kept on thinking what the hell the writer was thinking while writing this book. I had no idea who Kafka was then.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Karlštejn castle</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/karls%CC%8Ctejn-castle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/karls%CC%8Ctejn-castle/</guid>
      <description>There is no shortage of castles in Czech Republic and one of the castles you might wanna add to your list is Karlštejn castle. Why? Because the village it is located at, also called Karlštejn, is amazingly beautiful and also, it is only 30 Km or 19 miles from Prague. It could easily be a half day trip from Prague. Founded in mid 1300, nobody knows who actually built it. Strange.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Petrin Tower (Rozhledna), Prague</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/petrin-tower/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/petrin-tower/</guid>
      <description>The Petrin tower aka the Eiffel tower of Prague is about 60 meter tall steel framework tower in Prague. It does not seem tall enough. I know right. But Czech people are smart. The tower is located on the Petrin hill which makes it reasonably tall. Why did we visit it? Well, because I have not been to the Eiffel Tower yet. Going in January though and excited. That’s not the only reason.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malá Strana (Lesser Town), Prague</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/mala%CC%81-strana/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/mala%CC%81-strana/</guid>
      <description>Malá Strana also known as the Lesser Town is no less beautiful, though it is definitely less touristy than Old Town. Its name comes from the fact that it was the smaller half of Prague and is situated below the Castle on the left bank of the Vltava river and is connected to the larger towns of Prague by the Charles bridge.
  Beautiful district of Malá Strana with its cobblestoned streets   As always, we left our apartment in Prague early, around 8:30 AM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Klet’ Mountain</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/the-klet-mountain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/the-klet-mountain/</guid>
      <description>The Klet’ mountain is located near Cesky Krumlov, in the Southern Bohemian region of Czech Republic. Klet’ mountain is about 3556 feet/1084 meters, and you could see the Alps if the weather permits. Basically, it is perfect for connecting with the nature and you could observe the beautiful countryside from the top.
  The view from the Observatory tower of Klet’   Initially we had planned to go to Ceske Budejovice from Cesky Krumlov, but we both have missed the nature/hiking part so much, we decided it is time for a mountain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Český Krumlov</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/c%CC%8Cesky%CC%81-krumlov/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/c%CC%8Cesky%CC%81-krumlov/</guid>
      <description>Český Krumlov is a small fairy tale town in Czech Republic and can be done as a day trip from Prague, if you are okay commuting for 6 hours round trip by train/bus, but if you could spend a night here, just like we did, you would be just blown away.
  The fairytale town of Cesky Krumlov. Be prepared to take a lot of pictures   We took an early train at 8:02 AM to Cesky Krumlov from Prague and reached there at 10:50 AM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One day in Vienna</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/austria/one-day-in-vienna/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/austria/one-day-in-vienna/</guid>
      <description>One day in Vienna is obviously not enough, but D and I were courageous enough to do it despite being super tired from our previous trips. We had been out for three days already moving from Czech to Hungary and now to Austria.
  We took an early bus from Budapest..really early at 7 AM and reached Erdburg station of Vienna at 10 AM. Google map for public transportation does not work here though it is fine for walking and car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A day in Brno, Czech&#39;s second largest city</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/brno/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/brno/</guid>
      <description>Brno is the second largest city in Czech after Prague. It is about 2.5 hours by train from Prague. We took the morning train from Praha hl.n. at 6:55 AM and reached Brno hl.n. at 9:20 AM.
The public transport in Brno is amazing. So many trams and buses run inside the city, I was surprised. We quickly reached our Airbnb place and dumped our bags.
We were super hungry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Punkva Caves</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/punkva-caves/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/punkva-caves/</guid>
      <description>Whether you are a cave lover (you probably are if you are a Batman fan) or not, the Punkva caves would leave you mesmerized. I had no idea caves could be so beautiful too. One of the most visited localities of Czech Republic, the Punkva caves gave us a break from all the monuments and architectures we had been to in Czech in just a span of one week.
  The Macocha Abyss from the cave   Though Moravian Karst has many caves, only 5 of them are open to public and the Punkva caves are where people die to go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old Town (Stare Mesto), Prague</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/old-town/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/old-town/</guid>
      <description>If you want to travel back in time, say no more. Old Town in Prague will take you to the medieval times. This place is full of tourists as you would have guessed already. Therefore, D and I decided to leave early around 8:30 AM on a December morning. Yes, it was cold. We walked to the old town as it was only a 20 minute walk from our place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kutna Hora, a day trip from Prague</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/kutna-hora/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/kutna-hora/</guid>
      <description>So, you want to take a day trip from Prague. Say no more. Kutna Hora, a central Bohemian region situated in the east of Prague, is a medieval center boasting a variety of architectural monuments, which have been well preserved over time. It was the second most important town after Prague in the kingdom of Bohemia.
D and I decided to leave as early as possible even though it was cold, but whatever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Naplavka Farmers’ Market, Prague</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/pragues-farmers-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/pragues-farmers-market/</guid>
      <description>If you are here in Prague for a good amount of days, you must visit one of the farmer’s market held on Saturdays at Square I.P. Pavlova, Square Jiriho z Podebrad or at the riverbank near Palackeho namesti. It is a great way to enjoy the atmosphere, meet locals, and taste local food.
D and I decided to go to Naplavka Farmer’s market, which is right on the Vltava riverbank. The address is Náplavka, 128 00 Praha 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seward, Alaska</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/u.s.a./alaska/seward/seward-alaska/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/u.s.a./alaska/seward/seward-alaska/</guid>
      <description>Alaska is beautiful and I know I am stating the obvious. D and I always wanted to go to Alaska but the problem was we do not have a driving license. Hey, we are working on that part. As they say, “Where there is a will, there is a way”, we found out cabs do work fine in some parts of Alaska. No Uber though. We planned out everything a month ahead.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>