<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Serbia on WST</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/serbia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Serbia on WST</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/serbia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kalemegdan park and Belgrade fortress</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/serbia/kalemegdan-park-and-belgrade-fortress/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/serbia/kalemegdan-park-and-belgrade-fortress/</guid>
      <description>Kalemegdan Park is the Central Park of Belgrade, which means it is the largest and most beautiful park in Belgrade. It name comes from two Turkish words: Kale meaning fortress and megdan meaning battlefield. Kalemegdan park is basically a part of the Belgrade fortress and if there is only one thing you could do in Belgrade, it has to be visiting this fortress along with the park.
  Kalemegdan Park Fortress   HISTORY OF THE BELGRADE FORTRESS</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knez Mihailova Street, Belgrade</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/serbia/knez-mihailova-street-belgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/serbia/knez-mihailova-street-belgrade/</guid>
      <description>If you wanna feel the pulse of Belgrade, take a walk on the most vibrant street of this city, Knez Mihailova Street, which starts at Terazije Square and ends at Kalemegdan Park.
  Knez	Mihailova	Street   Knez Mihailova Street named after Mihailo Obrenović III, Prince of Serbia, is the main pedestrian and shopping zone protected by the law as the oldest and most valuable landmark of Belgrade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kosancicev venac, Belgrade</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/serbia/kosancicev-venac-belgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/serbia/kosancicev-venac-belgrade/</guid>
      <description>Kosancicev venac is the oldest urban neighborhood in Belgrade, where I am staying at present. Right now it is under construction, but that doesn’t take away its charm. Its Turkish cobblestones, cafes, galleries, and wineries give it the atmosphere of the 19th century.
  The neighborhood of Kosancicev venac ST. MICHAEL’S CATHEDRAL/SABORNA CRKVA
Though it is not the center of the city, it is close to many important landmarks like Kalemegdan park and fortress, Knez Mihailova Street, Republic Square in Belgrade, and this neighborhood boasts of one of the most beautiful Orthodox churches in the world, called St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Novi Sad, Serbia</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/serbia/novisad-belgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/serbia/novisad-belgrade/</guid>
      <description>Novi Sad is the second largest city in Serbia after Belgrade, famous for its Exit festival. It is on the banks of the Danube River and is absolutely gorgeous to the point that if there were such competition as being the most beautiful city in Serbia, it would give a very healthy competition to Belgrade. Being only 58 miles/94 Km from Belgrade, it makes a perfect day trip from Belgrade, though spending a night or two would be good too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Republic Square, Belgrade</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/serbia/republic-square-belgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/serbia/republic-square-belgrade/</guid>
      <description>Republic Square is one of the most common meeting points for both locals and visitors. If you are going on a tour with a local tour company, they would ask you to meet them “Under the Horse” which is just another name for Republic Square. Why? Because of the Monument to Prince Mihailo Obrenovic.
  Monument to Prince Mihailo Obrenovic. You can see why it’s called “Under the Horse   Besides the statue of Prince Mihailo, you can also find the National Museum and the National Theatre at Republic Square.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skadarlija/Bohemian quarter, Belgrade</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/serbia/skadarlija-bohemian-quarter-belgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/serbia/skadarlija-bohemian-quarter-belgrade/</guid>
      <description>Skadarlija is a vintage street close to the city center of Belgrade. It is also called Bohemian quarter similar to Paris’ Montmartre. Though it is not as bohemian in nature as it was once, it has still maintained its old atmosphere and spirit to some extent and you can find cobblestone pavements here.
  Skadarlija street   This street is named after the old Serbian town Skadar, which is on the territory of Albania today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Church of Saint Sava, Belgrade</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/serbia/church-of-saint-sava/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/serbia/church-of-saint-sava/</guid>
      <description>The Church of Saint Sava, dedicated to Saint Sava, is one of the largest Orthodox churches in the world and the largest in the Balkans, located on the Vračar plateau in Belgrade. It is a pretty impressive church, looking majestic from the outside with its bright white walls, golden crosses and plump domes, but going inside, you feel a little disappointed as it is not completed yet. It is called the Basílica de la Sagrada Familia of Barcelona for obvious reasons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nikola Tesla Museum, Belgrade</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/serbia/nikola-tesla-museum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/serbia/nikola-tesla-museum/</guid>
      <description>Nikola Tesla is my all time favorite scientists and if you are into science, I am sure you admire him too. For those people who don&amp;rsquo;t know much about Tesla, he was born in a Serbian family in a Croatian town of Smiljan in 1856. This is the reason why both Serbia and Croatia are so proud of him. In Serbia, he is like everywhere from Tesla TV to Tesla 100 Dinar bill.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>