<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Paris on WST</title>
    <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/cities/paris/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Paris on WST</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://whileshetravels.github.io/cities/paris/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Luxembourg Garden/Jardin du Luxembourg</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/luxembourg-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/luxembourg-garden/</guid>
      <description>Luxembourg Garden is nothing you have not seen before, but to find such a spacious place in Paris which is ideal for both children and adults is not easy, and that’s what makes this garden so special.
  Just relaxing in the garden with the view of the Palace   Luxembourg Garden is situated on the Left Bank and it is well maintained. It has a lot of benches and chairs and we were just sitting there for almost an hour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disneyland Paris</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/disneyland-paris/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/disneyland-paris/</guid>
      <description>We were really tired doing this sightseeing and wanted to do something different. Having never been the Disneyland Florida before, we thought let’s try the one here in Paris. We knew this one is not as good as the one in Florida after doing a ton of research, but it was worth a shot and I was in a mood of some adrenaline rush.
   View this post on Instagram         A post shared by @whileshetravels on Jan 31, 2017 at 11:27am PST</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Notre Dame de Paris</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/notre-dame-de-paris/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/notre-dame-de-paris/</guid>
      <description>Notre Dame de Paris meaning “Our Lady of Paris” is one of the largest and famous churches in the world. It is a fine example of Gothic architecture and being in Paris, if you do not see the Notre Dame de Paris, even just the cathedral which is free, it is really your loss. If possible, make sure you go all the way up the tower (not free) and admire the city of lights and gargoyles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eating in Paris and around..</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/eating-in-paris-and-around/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/eating-in-paris-and-around/</guid>
      <description>We landed in Paris on January 4th and have been trying different restaurants since then. Never been disappointed even once. We could settle in Paris just for its food.
  Restaurant: Le Drop Café; Item: Croquette and fries     Restaurant: Le Bistrot des Augustins; Item: Salmon Gratin     Bakery: Ladurée; Item: Chocolate Hazelnut Macaron     Restaurant: A Deux Pas d’lci in La Havre; Item: Cod fillet with tart apples and new potatoes     Restaurant: A Deux Pas d’lci in La Havre; Crumble perry and chocolate praline     Cafe: La Palette; Item: Coffee eclair     Cafe: Strada cafe; Item: Breakfast of Champions     Cafe: Strada cafe; Item: Hot Chocolate     Restaurant: Traiteur Marocain at Marché des Enfants Rouges; Item: Couscous Kefta     Cafe: Le Lafon; Item: Mousse au chocolat     Restaurant: Le Korrigan; Item: Savory crepe     Restaurant: Le Korrigan; Item: Chocolate crepe     Restaurant: Chez Gladines; Item: Squids in basque sauce with potatoes     Restaurant: Boulettes; Item: Cod fish meatballs with mashed potatoes     Restaurant: Auguste (1 Michelin Star); Item: Gaspache de tomates et pastèques 100% naturel Pickles de betteraves couleurs     Restaurant: Auguste (1 Michelin Star); Lieu jaune, pistou de salicorne Minestrone de petits pois “téléphone”     Restaurant: Auguste (1 Michelin Star); Item: Soufflé Grand Marnier Glace au fromage blanc     Restaurant: Le Dénicheur; Item: Tomato Soupe du jour     Restaurant: Le Dénicheur; Item: Fondant Au Chocolate Coeur Praline     Restaurant: Le Cafe; Item: Tartare de Saumon     Cafe: Le Porte Pot; Item: Tuna     Restaurant: Garance (1 Michelin Star); Item: Pomme purée     Restaurant: Garance (1 Michelin Star); Item: Cod fish     Restaurant: Garance (1 Michelin Star); Item: Chocolate dessert     Restaurant: Le Boui Boui; Item: Petit camenbert with fig     Restaurant: Le Boui Boui; Item: Sorbets     Restaurant: La Cave Gourmande; Item: Fish soup     Restaurant: Au Petit Suisse; Item: Tuna with homemade ratatouille and pasta     Restaurant: Au Petit Suisse; Item: French Onion soup   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crécy-la-Chapelle</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/cre%CC%81cy-la-chapelle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/cre%CC%81cy-la-chapelle/</guid>
      <description>If you are in Paris and have seen everything, and want to get away from the City of lights and its crowd for some time, Crécy-la-Chapelle would be an ideal place to do so.
  Crécy-la-Chapelle   Crécy-la-Chapelle is a small town and you can call it a mini Venice. It takes only an hour from Paris. We had been thinking to visit this town since some time and after missing our train to Mont Saint Michel, we finally did it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mont Saint-Michel, the trip which we couldn’t make it.</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/mont-saint-michel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/mont-saint-michel/</guid>
      <description>Le Mont Saint-Michel, an island commune in Normandy, is one of the most popular day trips from Paris and obviously, we had our heart set on it long before we came to Paris. It is situated in the middle of the bay and is famous for its abbey and having been to Etretat, another commune in Normandy, I was super excited for Mont Saint-Michel. I am sorry I got no picture to show and don’t want to use any Google image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musée de l’Armée and Napoleon’s Tomb</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/musee-d-larmee-and-napoleons-tomb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/musee-d-larmee-and-napoleons-tomb/</guid>
      <description>The Musée de l’Armée or the Army museum as the name suggests exhibits France’s complete military history along with the tomb of Napoleon. It is a perfect place if you love history. Even if you do not, you should visit this museum just for Napoleon, the man who conquered almost every part of Europe.
We left at 11 in the morning and took metro, line 8 and got off at La Tour Mauborg.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musée d Louvre, Paris</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/musee-d-louvre/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/musee-d-louvre/</guid>
      <description>If you are an art lover, you don’t need any introduction to the Musée du Louvre, and if you are not, this is the museum where you find the famous Mona Lisa, Venus de Milo and more than 30,000 work of arts. We visited the Louvre after the Musée d&amp;rsquo;Orsay, which was not in the right order actually. The Louvre museum houses the art works from the ancient world to 1850 and the Orsay museum got stuff from 1850 onwards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Père Lachaise Cemetery</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/pe%CC%80re-lachaise-cemetery/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/pe%CC%80re-lachaise-cemetery/</guid>
      <description>Père Lachaise Cemetery is one of the most peaceful cemeteries I have ever been to not to mention it is quite big and free, and in the month of January, it was so calm that it gave a kind of an eerie feeling. I know all cemeteries do. It got about 5000 trees and does look like a park. It is a star cemetery filled with the tombs of Oscar Wilde to Jim Morrison.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Champs-Élysées</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/champs-e%CC%81lyse%CC%81es/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/champs-e%CC%81lyse%CC%81es/</guid>
      <description>I have always heard about the Avenue des Champs-Élysées pronounced as Shon-zay-LEE-zay, that how grand and Parisian this avenue is. Taking a stroll around this avenue on a rainy January night made me feel a Parisian too, temporarily. We took metro line 9 and got off at Franklin D Roosevelt and that’s where the Avenue des Champs-Élysées started.
  The Avenue of Champs-Élysées   Known for its cafes, theaters, branded shops, Bastille Day Military Parade and the Tour de France, Avenue des Champs-Élysées stretches between Place de la Concorde and the Arc de Triomphe, which is one of the most famous monuments in Paris.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Montmartre</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/montmartre/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/montmartre/</guid>
      <description>Montmartre is a hill situated in Paris’ 18 arrondissement and this neighborhood is quite different from the arrondissement we had been to. It is trendy, crowded, and kind of seedy, and a place where many famous people have lived or worked from Van Gogh to Pablo Picasso. Even now, there are many artists and portraitists working here to exhibit and sell their artwork.
  The view of Paris from the hill     Clear skies would have been better   We left on a Saturday afternoon using metro, line 4 and got off at Barbes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pont des Arts, Paris</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/pont-des-arts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/pont-des-arts/</guid>
      <description>Pont des Arts is that famous bridge where couples used to make their love for each other memorable by attaching love lock with their names engraved or written to the railing or the grate of the bridge and tossing the keys into the Seine river below. No, this trend did not start centuries ago. It was pretty recent. The year was 2008.
  The bridge links the domed Institut de France to the Louvre museum   I might have done the same with D though he would have disapproved for sure, but since 2014, the locks have been removed as they’re damaging the bridge with their weights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Château de Versailles</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/versailles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/versailles/</guid>
      <description>Versailles is one of the most exquisite palaces of the world and a clear example of how pretentious kings used to be in the past. Started as a hunting lodge by Louis XIII in 1623, the Sun King, Louis XIV spent a great deal of money to convert his dad’s lodge into a grand palace.
  This whole damn thing looks like it is made of gold.   If you ask anyone for a day trip from Paris, Versailles would be the number one answer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Étretat, France</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/e%CC%81tretat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/e%CC%81tretat/</guid>
      <description>I was looking for a day trip from Paris and Étretat attracted me right away. It is a beautiful small town in Normandie region of France, with pebble beaches and unique shaped cliffs and arches. It takes about 3.5 hours one way from Paris to reach Etretat. I do not think I can justify its beauty in my post, but I would try and pictures would help.
  The serenity!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musée d&#39;Orsay, Paris</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/musee-d-orsay/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/france/musee-d-orsay/</guid>
      <description>Honestly, I have never been a museum enthusiast, but Paris is kind of a mecca of museums with the work of many world famous artists. The first place I visited in Paris was Musée d&amp;rsquo;Orsay pronounced as mew-zay-dor-say. Being one of the largest art museums in Paris, it houses the work of Manet, Monet, Cézanne, Van Gogh, Rodin, Gauguin and many other famous artists. You would find Impressionism at its best here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>