<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Iceland on WST</title>
    <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/tags/iceland/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Iceland on WST</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://whileshetravels.github.io/tags/iceland/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Iceland road trip itinerary</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/iceland-road-trip-itinerary/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/iceland-road-trip-itinerary/</guid>
      <description>I am sure you must have had several road trips in your life because come on who does not like a road trip? Right? But honestly, the one in Iceland is nothing like you have had before. It is beautiful to such an extent that it feels surreal. Yes, you might have seen like unlimited pictures of Iceland by now because these days Iceland is a hot tourist spot, but let me tell you something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iceland road trip: Day 1, April 23, 2017</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-1/</guid>
      <description>Driving route: Southwest to Northwest Attractions: No major attractions really Campsite for the night: Ólafsvik campsite We had our flight to Iceland Keflavik International airport at 8 AM from Copenhagen International airport. It was a 3.5 hour flight. The flight was 40% empty. We reached Keflavik around 9:30 AM. Yes, it is 2 hour behind the Central European time zone.
  Flying away to my dream destination   We had scheduled a pickup from our camper car company, which is Kuku Campers (read more about them here) at 10:00 AM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iceland road trip: Day 2, April 24, 2017</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-2/</guid>
      <description>Driving route: Northwest to North Attractions: Kirkjufell Mountain and Eiríksstadir farmhouse Campsite for the night: Hamrar in Akureyri On day 2 of our Iceland road trip, we woke up to this in our camper car at the campsite Olafsvik.
  We stepped outside and it was chilly and beautiful. Everything was covered with a thin sheet of snow and it seemed white mountains are calling me. But before that, we had to have our breakfast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iceland road trip: Day 3, April 25, 2017</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-3/</guid>
      <description>Driving route: North to East Attractions: Godafoss waterfall, Mývatn lake area (Skútustaðagígar pseudo craters, Dimmuborgir, Grjotagja Cave, Myvatn nature bath, and Mt. Námafjall) Campsite for the night: Egilsstadir Camping site Having slept soundly previous night at Hamrar campsite in Akureyri, we woke up fresh and all set to explore the east Iceland. But first thing first. We took shower which was what we really needed. Then, we fixed ourselves some eggs and bread in the kitchen of our campsite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iceland road trip: Day 4, April 26, 2017</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-4/</guid>
      <description>Driving route: East to South East Attractions: Jökulsárlón - Glacier Lagoon Campsite for the night: Vatnajökull National Park campsite Day 4 was the sunniest and hottest day in Iceland for us, and also the most beautiful day. Our objective for today was to reach south east and camp at Skaftafell National Park, which is actually a part of Vatnajökull National Park now.
Our last night campsite, Egilsstadir, was equipped with hot shower.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iceland road trip: Day 5, April 27, 2017</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-5/</guid>
      <description>Driving route: South East to south Attractions: Vatnajökull glacier, Svartifoss waterfall, Fjaðrárgljúfur canyon, Laufskálavarða, Mossy Lava Rock Black Sand Beach, Skogafoss Campsite for the night: Gesthús Selfoss Campsite We spent the last night in the parking lot of the Vatnajökull National Park. Vatnajökull is the largest glacier in Europe and you can even do glacier hiking, if you like that sort of things. You can find two different tour companies in the National park itself which do glacier hiking and ice caving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iceland road trip: Day 6, April 28, 2017</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-6/</guid>
      <description>Driving route: South to Southwest (Golden Circle) Attractions: Þingvellir National Park, Geysir, Gullfoss waterfall Campsite for the night: Gesthús Selfoss Campsite It was Friday and day 6 of our Iceland road trip. Weather was not looking good for today. There was a high speed wind warning in the south. So, we wanted to keep things calm and light for today. We woke up sort of late. It had rained all night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iceland road trip: Day 7, April 29, 2017</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-7/</guid>
      <description>Driving route: South to Southwest (Golden Circle) Attractions: Kerið crater lake, Skalholt, Secret Lagoon, Laugarvatn Fontana, Hrunalaug hot spring, Brúarfoss, Faxi (waterfall) Campsite for the night: Gesthús Selfoss Campsite Day 7 was our last day with our camping car. We were supposed to drop it off the next day in the morning. There were few things we wanted to cover, but to a large extent, we had kept this day open to see things as we drive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reykjavik, Iceland: Day 8, April 30, 2017</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-8/</guid>
      <description>Driving route: Gesthús Selfoss campsite to Kuku campers. Kuku campers to Reykjavik by bus. Attractions: Laugavegur shopping and dining area Campsite for the night: No campsite. Finally an Airbnb place. So, it was almost all over. Our Iceland road trip. And not only that, our 5 months of country hopping was coming to an end too. We weren&amp;rsquo;t thinking a lot about going back to the US at this time though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reykjavik, Iceland: Day 9, May 1, 2017</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/iceland/day-9/</guid>
      <description>Attractions: Hallgrimskirkja, Solfar/Sun Voyager sculpture, Harpa Reykjavik Concert Hall and Conference Centre, Lake Tjornin It was raining hard on day 9, which was also our last day of our Iceland trip. To be more precise, the whole Euro trip. We did not want to go out really, but of course, we did go out. I did not want to waste my last day just like that.
Our first stop was Hallgrimskirkja, a Lutheran Parish church, which also happens to be the tallest church in Iceland.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>