<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>San Pedro De Atacama on WST</title>
    <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/tags/san-pedro-de-atacama/</link>
    <description>Recent content in San Pedro De Atacama on WST</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://whileshetravels.github.io/tags/san-pedro-de-atacama/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Altaplantis Lagoons</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/chile/san-pedro-de-atacama/altipanic-lakes-hike/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/chile/san-pedro-de-atacama/altipanic-lakes-hike/</guid>
      <description>Tour Operator Guide Time     Chakana tours Jaime 6:00 - 15:00    Chaxa Lagoon Altitude: 2300m
  Had three kinds of flamingos. Learned that flamingoes Andean, James, and Chilean
Flamingos are pink or orange or white depending on what they eat. Flamingos eat algae and crustaceans that contain pigments called carotenoids. For the most part, these pigments are found in the brine shrimp and blue-green algae that the birds eat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geysors El Tatio</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/chile/san-pedro-de-atacama/geysors-el-tatio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/chile/san-pedro-de-atacama/geysors-el-tatio/</guid>
      <description>Tour Operator Guide Time     Andes Travels Jaime 5:00 - 13:00    Height: 4320m
  Dress: Layers of clothes and multiple socks. The ground is literally freezing.
Restrooms: Are pretty cleaned and widely available
Animals seen: Lamas and Fox and Vicuña and Lamas
Caution: Altitude sickness so walk slowly and small steps Drink a lot of water.
Stopped at a Machucha to have Queso De Cabra (Empananadas with Goat Cheese) very delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lascar Volcano hike</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/chile/san-pedro-de-atacama/lascar-volcano-hike/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/chile/san-pedro-de-atacama/lascar-volcano-hike/</guid>
      <description>Láscar volcano in northern Chile is the most active of the northern Chilean Andes. Lascar is an andesitic-to-dacitic stratovolcano with 3 overlapping summit craters. Large lava flows are visible on its NW flanks. Lascar is flanked 5 km to the east by the older, but higher Volcán Aguas Calientes stratovolcano.
  Crater   The most important ones are Licancabut, Sairecabur, Llullolico (the three at the international border), Lascar, Paniri, Linzor volcanoes stand at 5500m above sea levels, therefore it is fundamental to spend a few days adaoptinh to the altitude.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moon and Death Valley</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/chile/san-pedro-de-atacama/moon-and-death-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/chile/san-pedro-de-atacama/moon-and-death-valley/</guid>
      <description>Moon valley It is one of the most visited places in San Pedro and it is located at 17 kilometers of San Pedro&amp;rsquo;s downtown, in the Cordillera de la Sal (Salt mountains) area, is an interesting area with stones and sand formations that per millenia the floods and the winds have given it a series of colors and texture to the desert, it presents an extraordinary attractive by its similarity with the moon surface and the natural coliseo of great dimensions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Pedro de Atacama Itinerary</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/chile/san-pedro-de-atacama/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/chile/san-pedro-de-atacama/summary/</guid>
      <description>The most arid desert in th world, the Atcama Desert. The archealogoical capital of Chile is located at tee base of the High Lands, at the basin of the San Pedro River(the biggest river to reach the Atacam Salt Flats). The basins borders the Domeyko Mountain Range to the west and the high plateau or Altiplano of the Andes Mountain Range or the Puna de Atacam to the east</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>