<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Prague on WST</title>
    <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/tags/prague/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Prague on WST</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://whileshetravels.github.io/tags/prague/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Where to stay in Prague</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/where-to-stay-in-prague/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/where-to-stay-in-prague/</guid>
      <description>To be honest, I don’t have any idea about hotels in Prague as we never stayed at any of them. We were going to be in Prague for more than a month (33 nights) and needed a furnished apartment/studio where we could live somewhat like locals.
We did an extensive research on different websites and were able to find a great studio in an excellent location for 24,000 CZK for 33 nights at https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charles Bridge, Prague</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/charles-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/charles-bridge/</guid>
      <description>Charles Bridge is one of the most popular attractions in Prague. I don’t know what it is but there is something unique in the atmosphere on this bridge. It is too lively and everyone is super happy.
  Attempting to dab in the middle of the Charles Bridge! Not my fault. D forced me to.   Charles Bridge was built under Charles IV in 1357 and completed in 1402.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prague Castle Complex, Prague</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/prague-castle-complex/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/prague-castle-complex/</guid>
      <description>If you are in Prague and have not visited the castle, have you really been to Prague? The answer is no. Yes, we waited like forever to visit the famous castle for some unknown reason, but nonetheless, we did it and guess what we were rewarded with for our patience? Snow and a lot of it. Prague Castle is not just a castle but a castle complex and the largest one too in the world with an area of almost 70,000 meter squares.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prague Zoo, Prague</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/prague-zoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/prague-zoo/</guid>
      <description>Honestly, I was not expecting a lot from the zoo in Prague and I don’t even know why. Maybe because I thought Prague is all about the castle and cathedrals. I could not be more wrong. Prague zoo is full of exotic animals and it is well maintained with a lot of restrooms and cafes and restaurants. Also, it is a perfect getaway from the crowd and the various sightseeings we have been doing since a long time, and if you are in Prague with your kids, this is a place you must visit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Franz Kafka Museum, Prague</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/franz-kafka-museum/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/franz-kafka-museum/</guid>
      <description>“I am a cage, in search of a bird.” ― Franz Kafka
I read “Metamorphosis” by Franz Kafka in the summer of 2013 and honestly, I had never read a book like that. It did not make much sense to me and yet kept me intrigued. All that time I was reading, I kept on thinking what the hell the writer was thinking while writing this book. I had no idea who Kafka was then.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Karlštejn castle</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/karls%CC%8Ctejn-castle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/karls%CC%8Ctejn-castle/</guid>
      <description>There is no shortage of castles in Czech Republic and one of the castles you might wanna add to your list is Karlštejn castle. Why? Because the village it is located at, also called Karlštejn, is amazingly beautiful and also, it is only 30 Km or 19 miles from Prague. It could easily be a half day trip from Prague. Founded in mid 1300, nobody knows who actually built it. Strange.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Petrin Tower (Rozhledna), Prague</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/petrin-tower/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/petrin-tower/</guid>
      <description>The Petrin tower aka the Eiffel tower of Prague is about 60 meter tall steel framework tower in Prague. It does not seem tall enough. I know right. But Czech people are smart. The tower is located on the Petrin hill which makes it reasonably tall. Why did we visit it? Well, because I have not been to the Eiffel Tower yet. Going in January though and excited. That’s not the only reason.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malá Strana (Lesser Town), Prague</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/mala%CC%81-strana/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/mala%CC%81-strana/</guid>
      <description>Malá Strana also known as the Lesser Town is no less beautiful, though it is definitely less touristy than Old Town. Its name comes from the fact that it was the smaller half of Prague and is situated below the Castle on the left bank of the Vltava river and is connected to the larger towns of Prague by the Charles bridge.
  Beautiful district of Malá Strana with its cobblestoned streets   As always, we left our apartment in Prague early, around 8:30 AM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Klet’ Mountain</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/the-klet-mountain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/the-klet-mountain/</guid>
      <description>The Klet’ mountain is located near Cesky Krumlov, in the Southern Bohemian region of Czech Republic. Klet’ mountain is about 3556 feet/1084 meters, and you could see the Alps if the weather permits. Basically, it is perfect for connecting with the nature and you could observe the beautiful countryside from the top.
  The view from the Observatory tower of Klet’   Initially we had planned to go to Ceske Budejovice from Cesky Krumlov, but we both have missed the nature/hiking part so much, we decided it is time for a mountain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Český Krumlov</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/c%CC%8Cesky%CC%81-krumlov/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/c%CC%8Cesky%CC%81-krumlov/</guid>
      <description>Český Krumlov is a small fairy tale town in Czech Republic and can be done as a day trip from Prague, if you are okay commuting for 6 hours round trip by train/bus, but if you could spend a night here, just like we did, you would be just blown away.
  The fairytale town of Cesky Krumlov. Be prepared to take a lot of pictures   We took an early train at 8:02 AM to Cesky Krumlov from Prague and reached there at 10:50 AM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A day in Brno, Czech&#39;s second largest city</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/brno/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/brno/</guid>
      <description>Brno is the second largest city in Czech after Prague. It is about 2.5 hours by train from Prague. We took the morning train from Praha hl.n. at 6:55 AM and reached Brno hl.n. at 9:20 AM.
The public transport in Brno is amazing. So many trams and buses run inside the city, I was surprised. We quickly reached our Airbnb place and dumped our bags.
We were super hungry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Punkva Caves</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/punkva-caves/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/punkva-caves/</guid>
      <description>Whether you are a cave lover (you probably are if you are a Batman fan) or not, the Punkva caves would leave you mesmerized. I had no idea caves could be so beautiful too. One of the most visited localities of Czech Republic, the Punkva caves gave us a break from all the monuments and architectures we had been to in Czech in just a span of one week.
  The Macocha Abyss from the cave   Though Moravian Karst has many caves, only 5 of them are open to public and the Punkva caves are where people die to go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old Town (Stare Mesto), Prague</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/old-town/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/old-town/</guid>
      <description>If you want to travel back in time, say no more. Old Town in Prague will take you to the medieval times. This place is full of tourists as you would have guessed already. Therefore, D and I decided to leave early around 8:30 AM on a December morning. Yes, it was cold. We walked to the old town as it was only a 20 minute walk from our place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kutna Hora, a day trip from Prague</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/kutna-hora/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/kutna-hora/</guid>
      <description>So, you want to take a day trip from Prague. Say no more. Kutna Hora, a central Bohemian region situated in the east of Prague, is a medieval center boasting a variety of architectural monuments, which have been well preserved over time. It was the second most important town after Prague in the kingdom of Bohemia.
D and I decided to leave as early as possible even though it was cold, but whatever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Naplavka Farmers’ Market, Prague</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/pragues-farmers-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/czech/pragues-farmers-market/</guid>
      <description>If you are here in Prague for a good amount of days, you must visit one of the farmer’s market held on Saturdays at Square I.P. Pavlova, Square Jiriho z Podebrad or at the riverbank near Palackeho namesti. It is a great way to enjoy the atmosphere, meet locals, and taste local food.
D and I decided to go to Naplavka Farmer’s market, which is right on the Vltava riverbank. The address is Náplavka, 128 00 Praha 2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>