<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Romania on WST</title>
    <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/countries/romania/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Romania on WST</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://whileshetravels.github.io/countries/romania/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Brasov, a medieval city surrounded by the Carpathian Mountains</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/brasov/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/brasov/</guid>
      <description>Brasov pronounced as Bra-Shov is one of the most visited cities of Romania. Located in the center of Romania, it makes a perfect base for exploring the surrounding regions and trust me, you do wanna go see those surrounding regions. Why? Well, I am sure your trip to Romania is incomplete without visiting the Bran Castle and Bran castle is only a 40 minute bus ride from Brasov. Similarly, there are many other cool things to see around Brasov, which I would mention later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hiking to the Seven Ladders Canyon, a unique experience near Brasov in Romania</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/seven-ladders-canyon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/seven-ladders-canyon/</guid>
      <description>Our Airbnb host suggested us to hike to the Seven Ladders Canyon also known Canionul Sapte Scari in Romania. 7 Laderrs Canyon lies in Piatra Mare Mountains and if you enjoy hiking and some adrenaline rush, this is the place you need to be. Many people visiting Brasov don’t know about it, but it is pretty popular with locals. We were staying for a total of 10 days in Brasov and we thought why not, let’s do some hiking, which would be a good change from all the sightseeings we’d been doing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the villages of Romania, not far from Sibiu ( Marginimea Sibiului)</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/marginimea-sibiului/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/marginimea-sibiului/</guid>
      <description>Marginimea Sibiului which means “ Borders of Sibiu” is an area which is made up of 18 villages. Set at the foothills of the Cindrel Mountains, the villages are known for preserving the ethnological, cultural, architectural, and historical heritage of Romania. Even now, people wear traditional Romanian costumes, and their occupation is shepherding. They take the sheep to the mountains in summer and bring them back to the village in winter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peles Castle, day trip from Brasov</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/peles-castle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/peles-castle/</guid>
      <description>Bran castle is interesting and all thanks to Bram Stoker and Vlad the impaler, but honestly it is a rather simple castle and one not so impressive. Many people come out from there disappointed. If you really wanna see a castle at a grand level near Brasov, you should head to a town of Sinaia and walk to the Peles castle. It is one of the most picturesque and stylish castles in Europe, with extremely well-preserved architecture, details and furniture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alba Iulia, day trip from Sibiu</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/alba-iulia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/alba-iulia/</guid>
      <description>We first came to know about Alba Iulia from our Airbnb host, Diana, in Timisoara. We had to go to Sibiu from Timisoara and the bus ride was about 6 hours. Diana suggested we go to Alba Iulia first, stay there for a night, and then go to Sibiu. It did not work out for us as we had already booked an Airbnb apartment in Sibiu. In Sibiu, our host also mentioned Alba Iulia that we can easily do a day trip from Sibiu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bran castle and Rasnov citadel, day trip from Brasov</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/bran-castle-and-rasnov-citadel-a-day-trip-from-brasov/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/bran-castle-and-rasnov-citadel-a-day-trip-from-brasov/</guid>
      <description>When you are in Romania, and haven’t visited Bran castle aka Dracula’s castle, nobody would believe you have been to Romania. Romania is famous for its Dracula’s story and Vlad the impaler, who has been referred to as a vampire/Dracula due to his torture methods, but obviously, those are just legends, which became popular due to Bram Stoker’s novel, Dracula. Romania is famous for all the wrong reasons, it seems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Balea Lake in winter, a day trip from Sibiu</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/balea-lake/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/balea-lake/</guid>
      <description>Balea lake is a glacier lake close to Sibiu. It takes about an hour to get there by car. Situated at the height of 2,034 m in the Fagaras mountains, it is covered with snow for most part. In summer, you can drive to it via the Transfăgărășan road. We really wanted to drive through the Transfăgărășan road, but it is open only from July to September, unfortunately, due to heavy snow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sibiu, an idyllic medieval town in Romania</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/sibiu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/sibiu/</guid>
      <description>Sibiu was our second destination in Romania, first being Timisoara. Both the cities are so distinct from each other. Where Timisoara is a big city by the standard of Romania, Sibiu is more like a town, to be more precise, a German town, with a total population of 147,245. Sibiu is located in Transylvania region, which is the most interesting part of Romania. It was one of the seven cities in Transylvania with German settlers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diana and John, our Airbnb hosts</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/diana-and-john-our-airbnb-hosts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/diana-and-john-our-airbnb-hosts/</guid>
      <description>It’s been 4 months since we left our apartment in San Francisco to travel Europe. We have been to many places, seen a lot of wonderful things, met some really interesting people, but something which we would never forget is the hospitality of Diana and John. We stayed with them for 2 nights at their apartment located centrally in Timisoara via Airbnb. We came as strangers and left as friends. Both Diana and John are lovely people and they make such a cute couple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sighisoara, day trip from Brasov</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/sighisoara-day-trip-from-brasov/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/sighisoara-day-trip-from-brasov/</guid>
      <description>Ever since coming to Romania, everybody kept talking about how we have to visit Sighisoara, the only living citadel in Europe. When we were in Sibiu, our guide suggested us to take us there, but we thought we would do this as a day trip from Brasov as we had more days there. In Brasov, one of the first things our Airbnb host told us was to go get lost in Sighisoara.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top things to do in Timisoara, Romania</title>
      <link>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/top-things-to-do-in-timisoara-romania/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://whileshetravels.github.io/post/romania/top-things-to-do-in-timisoara-romania/</guid>
      <description>We had heard and read a lot about Romania from the stories of Dracula to this country having one of the fastest internets in the world, and this was on our bucket list since a long time. The first city we decided to explore in Romania was Timisoara as it was only a 3 hour drive from Belgrade, where we stayed for 2 weeks. Timisoara is the third most populous country in Romania and being the European Cultural Capital for 2021, it offers a lot of things to do, and most of the important landmarks are situated in the city center or close to the city center.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>